https://www.naturaltraining.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We take your privacy on the Internet very seriously, and this document explains what personal data we capture and how we use it.
Information We Collect
We collect two types of information from site users: personal data (including names and e-mail addresses); and statistical data (e.g. how many users use the site, and which pages they view).
Personal Data
This is only captured when you provide it, such as when you register for our e-newsletter or enter a competition. We will send you emails containing news and information about our products and industry information that we feel you will be interested in. You may unsubscribe from the email at any time. Your email address and personal information will never be made available to another organisation for marketing purposes without your explicit consent.
Statistical Data
We may log your IP address as you browse the site. This is purely for website statistics, recording the users to the site and which pages they visit. This information does not tell us who you are, and we only use this to monitor the effectiveness of the site.
Data Protection
Natural Training seek to comply with the UK Data Protection Act 1998. We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of personal information so as to prevent unauthorised access by third parties.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us.
Comments are closed.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Necessary
Always Enabled
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
×
Just 3 quick details to reveal how competitive our prices are.
Email
Full Name
Telephone No
Don’t worry we will never share your details with any 3rd party.
Thank you.
